sheposts.com 2019-03-06

# Privacy Policy - TheStyleUp

## 1\. Introduction

Welcome to TheStyleUp! This Site is operated by TheStyleUp.com and has been created for users to stay on top of celebrity beauty trends, product reviews, and makeup tips. From the latest hairstyle trends to real girl makeovers, body modification includes tattoos, piercing, Daily Makeover reveals everyday tips and insider secrets to help you uncover your best look. This Privacy Policy sets forth TheStyleUp

policy with respect to information including personally identifiable data (“Personal Data”) and other information that is collected from Site visitors.

BY ACCESSING, USING AND/OR DOWNLOADING THE SITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND ALSO SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF OUR TERMS OF SERVICE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU SHOULD NOT ACCESS, DOWNLOAD AND/OR USE THE SITE. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy frequently, as it may change from time to time. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use the Site.

The Site is primarily operated from and hosted on servers located in the United States in accordance with laws of the United States. Users of the Site should be aware that the laws of the United States may differ from those of your country of residence. By using the Site, participating in any Site activities, and/or providing us with your personal information, you: (i) consent to the transfer and processing of any information you provide; (ii) acknowledge that U.S. law provides a lower standard of protection for personal data than the laws of various jurisdictions including, but not limited to, the European Union; and (iii) understand that we will treat your information in accordance with our Privacy Policy and U.S. law. Consequently, you hereby waive any claims that may arise under the laws and regulations that apply to you in any other jurisdiction.

## 2\. Personal Information We Collect

As you may have guessed, personal information is information that personally identifies you or allows us or others to contact you. In connection with your use of the Site, you may be asked to provide your name, email address, username, and password. Personal information also may include information that may not be personally identifiable standing alone, but which may become personally identifiable when combined with personal information. Some pages and features on our Site can be visited and used without providing any personal information. For other pages, functionalities and services, you may need to provide personal information. Personal information is only collected from you when you provide it.

Please do not share your life story (it’s not that we’re not interested, and we can’t stop you) when you submit a quote to us for consideration, create an account or otherwise use this Site. We will not disclose any personal information that you provide to us except in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

## 3\. Non-Personal Information We Collect

We may also collect information about you that is not personal information. When you access the Site, create an account and/or submit a quote, we may collect information such as your communication and other preferences, information about your computer, devices and Internet connection, IP address, browser, operating system, referring URL, metadata, specific pages that you access on the Site or prior to or after visiting the site, the length of time you spend at the site, and other general information about our visitors. This information, on its own, cannot usually be used to identify you. We may also collect non-personal information through the use of cookies, anonymous identifiers, pixel tags, web beacons, scripts, and other similar technologies, as further discussed below. We consider any non-personal information that has been combined with personal information to be personal information.

## 4\. Location Data

We may request access to or otherwise receive information about your device location when you access the Site. Your location data may be based on your IP address. We use location data in connection with providing the Site and to help improve user experience with the Site.

## 5\. Use of Information

We may freely use non-personal information or aggregate information for any lawful purpose. We also may use any information collected on or through our Site, including your personal information, (“Collected Information”) for various purposes, including printing physical paper copies of it and turning it into an origami hat (kidding again). All jokes aside, we and our third party service providers may use Collected Information to:

  * help administer the Site and the servers that provide the Site;
  * generate statistical information;
  * market, promote or advertise the Site, the Content or our subscription services;
  * monitor and analyze Site traffic and usage patterns;
  * improve the Site’s content and content delivery, including any online content, materials, and services that we
  * describe or make available on the Site;
  * register and administer your membership in our subscription service;
  * provide customer service and support;
  * verify communications from you, respond to your inquiries and otherwise communicate with you;
  * enforce our Terms of Service and contracts with third parties;
  * prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities or to otherwise comply with applicable laws and regulations; and
  * for any other purpose that is permissible or required under the law, that is disclosed to you at the point of collection of personal information, or for which you provide your prior consent.

We may specifically use IP addresses to provide aggregated data to advertisers about the volume of useage on the Site, to determine your general (but not precise) geographic location, to create and segment audiences and otherwise to target advertising, and to help identify and log potential malicious use of our Site.

We may also use Collected Information and the associated statistical data we and our third party service providers generate to deliver targeted advertisements to you and other visitors of the Site. We and our third party service providers may store Collected Information for as long as needed for the purposes indicated in this Privacy Policy, which may be indefinitely.

## 6\. Disclosure of Your Information

We may freely share and disclose aggregated and other non-personal information (including anonymized information and other non-personal information that is automatically collected as you navigate through and use the Site) without restriction as permitted by law. In particular, we may share Collected Information with certain of our third party service providers (e.g., our web hosting provider whose server logs collect the non-personal information described above) in order to provide the Site to you. We may also share Collected Information with some of our business and marketing partners in furthering our mission as an organization or delivering the content, materials, and services available on or through the Site to you. We and our third party service providers may also produce reports on Site traffic, usage patterns, and similar data generated from non-personal Collected Information, and we may share these reports with our business and marketing partners and others.

We reserve the right to use IP addresses to identify you and we may use and disclose any information about or relating to you, including any personal information about you, to third parties without your consent if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to: (1) comply with a court order, search warrant, subpoena, or other legal process; (2) to comply with legal, regulatory or administrative requirements of any governmental authorities; (3) otherwise fulfill a government or law enforcement request for information; (4) establish, defend or exercise our legal rights; (5) protect or defend the Site, users, or our subsidiaries and affiliates, and all of their respective officers, directors, employees, attorneys, agents, contractors, licensors, and partners, in connection with any actual or alleged legal action, claim or dispute; (6) respond to claims that any posting or other content of our Site violates the rights of third parties, including without limitation providing information necessary to satisfy the notice and counter-notice procedures pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act; (7) in an emergency, to protect the health and safety of our Site’s users or the general public; or (8) enforce compliance with our Terms of Service or other contractual obligations.

If all or part of our company is sold, merged, or otherwise transferred to another entity, we may transfer Collected Information to such entity as part of that transaction.

Every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may contract for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving the Site or its underlying files or systems. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you.

## 7\. Cookies and Beacons

Cookies aren’t just delicious; they also apparently have something to do with computers. Cookies help to improve your user experience and allow us to analyze our Site and to analyze and manage our advertising. These Cookies are placed on your computer when your web browser accesses the Site. While some cookies are deleted when you close your browser (session cookies), others remain even after you close your browsing session (persistent cookies).

We use cookies to save your preferences and to recognize you when you return to the Site. We also use analytics cookies to provide data about how users interact with our Site content and advertising campaigns, such as Site traffic. In addition, we use advertising cookies to manage, track, target and serve ads through our third-party service providers. You may not be able to access the full functionality of the Site if cookies are disabled on your browser.

Most web browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your web browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. The “Help” feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. For more information on how to manage browser cookies, see http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

We also use web beacons to monitor the traffic patterns of visitors from one TheStyleUp.com page to another. A web beacon is an object that is embedded in a web page and is usually invisible to you but allows us to confirm that you have viewed the web page.

We, our service providers and other third parties may analyze the information derived from cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, scripts and other technologies and match or combine that information with data provided by you or collected or received from public and commercial sources. Please note that to the extent that third parties are using pixel tags, cookies, beacons, scripts or other tracking technologies on our Site, we do not control the use of those technologies or the resulting information, the use of which are governed by the privacy policies of those third parties.

If you’re new to the Internet, please don’t try dunking your mouse in milk and eating it; this is the Number One complaint we get after users read our Privacy Policy.

## 8\. Online Tracking / “Do Not Track” Signals

Some web browsers may give you the ability to enable a “Do Not Track” setting that sends a special signal to the websites you encounter while web browsing that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. Our systems do not recognize browser “Do Not Track” signals. If we do so in the future, we will update this Privacy Policy to describe how we respond to such signals. We may work with third parties that use tracking technologies on the Site, including in order to serve tailored advertisements on our behalf and on behalf of other advertisers across the Internet. These and other third parties may collect information about your activity on the Site over time, as well as your interaction with our advertising and other communications, and use this information to determine which ads you see on third-party websites and apps based on your apparent interests. This is known as interest-based advertising. For more information about this practice and to understand your options, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/ or http://www.aboutads.info. To learn more about Do Not Track, visit http://www.allaboutdnt.com/.

## 9\. Our Third-Party Service Providers

Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies may place advertisements on the Site, and on the Internet generally, and may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about you. We do not control the use of such technology and have no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about you. Several of our service providers who utilize cookies and other tracking technologies on our Site enable you to opt out of their internet-based advertising.

While the companies we work with may change from time to time, below is a list of our current third-party service providers, which we allow to collect and use information about you through our Site:

  * Google Analytics, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to help us identify anonymous user interests, identify anonymous user demographics and to display advertising to previous visitors to this site. Google Analytics uses a cookie to provide analysis, anonymous interest data, and anonymous demographic data from visits to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the Google Analytics cookie by visiting the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Tool](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). Tracking of users through the Google Analytics cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.
  * We use Google DART to serve ads on the Site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.
  * We use RadiumOne to identify and collect anonymous user interests on our Site and to display targeted ads to users on our Site. For more information about RadiumOne and how it collects and processes data, please see RadiumOne’s Privacy Policy. You can opt-out of RadiumOne targeted advertising based on data collected via your browser by visiting the [RadiumOne Preference Manager](http://www.radiumone.com/opt/).
  * We use Sonobi to identify and collect anonymous user interests on our Site. For more information about Sonobi and how it collects and processes data, please visit its Privacy Policy. You may opt-out of Sonobi’s collection of data via your browser by visiting the [Sonobi Out-out page](https://sonobi.com/welcome/opt-out.php).
  * We use Yieldbot to identify anonymous user interests on our Site (starting to notice a pattern here?). For information about Yieldbot and how it collects and processes data, please visit its Privacy Policy. You may opt-out of Yieldbot’s collection of data via your browser by using the [Yieldbot Privacy Policy Opt-out](http://yieldbot.com/privacy-policy.html#opt-out).
  * We use Amazon to identify and collect anonymous user interests on our Site and to display ads to users on our Site. For information about Amazon and how it collects and processes data, please visit its Privacy Statement. You may opt-out of Amazon’s collection of data via your browser by visiting the [Amazon Advertising Preferences Opt-out](https://www.amazon.com/gp/dra/info).

Some of our digital advertising service providers are members of the Network Advertising Initiative or the Digital Advertising Alliance, each of which offer a single location to opt-out of certain ad targeting from member companies. To learn more about interest-based advertising generally as well as your options for opting out, please visit [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) or [About Ads](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). In addition, the Federal Trade Commission provides useful information about online privacy on its own website at [FTC Privacy Site](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/topics/privacy-identity). Please keep in mind that even if you opt out of receiving ads tailored to your apparent interests, you will continue to see ads from online advertising networks. However, those networks will not be able to apply any of your apparent ad preferences and the ads that you see therefore may be less relevant to your interests.

## 10\. Third Party Websites

We may link to third party websites from our own Site. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, these third party websites or their use of your personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites or ads and we are not responsible for the content found on or the actions or privacy practices employed by any other website or app.

The Site may also offer you the ability to interact with social plugins from social media sites, such as Facebook (facebook.com), Google+ (plus.google.com), Twitter (twitter.com), and Pinterest (pinterest.com). The social media sites may receive data when you visit a website that has plugins. In some cases, we may know that you clicked on a social plugin such as a Facebook Like button, or receive other information from the social media sites. Similarly, if you have previously provided personally identifiable information to a third-party operating a plug-in on this website, then this third-party may recognize you on the Site. Your use of social media plugins is subject to each social media site’s privacy policy, which may be different from ours.

We recommend that, if you have a ridiculous amount of free time (and nothing better to do), you review their privacy policies and other agreements governing your use of their website. Once you do, you should report back to us in a detailed and meticulously proofread memorandum explaining all of these websites, so we may immediately put it to use under that corner of the table that is lower than the rest.

## 11\. Law Enforcement

We may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith that it is desirable to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, or other legal matter. We may also use and disclose information about you to establish or exercise our legal rights, to assert and defend against legal claims, or if we believe such disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding actual or suspected illegal or fraudulent activities or potential threats to the physical safety or well-being of any person.

In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either. Chances are that if the police are looking into your activities on a quote website, you’ve really got issues.

## 12\. Security of Information

We make no guarantees as to the security or privacy of your information. It is in our interest to keep the Site secure, and we take reasonable steps to protect against the unauthorized access, disclosure, misuse, alteration and destruction of the personal information under our control. We recommend that you use anti-virus software, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats. If you become aware of any breach of Site security or this Privacy Policy, please notify us immediately. (Be the third pig, not one of the first two.)

## 13\. California Online Privacy Protection Act

Under Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, California residents that have an existing business relationship with us may request information about our disclosure of certain categories of personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, email us with the subject heading “California Privacy Rights.” In your request, please confirm that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response.

Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the California privacy rights requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve the right not to respond to requests submitted to addresses other than the email address specified in this section.

## 14\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change or update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and the amended version will be posted on the Site in place of the old version. You can identify the date that this Privacy Policy was last updated by looking at the date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will take effect upon posting to the Site. Use of the Site following posted changes constitutes your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy then in effect. If you do not agree to the new Privacy Policy, you must immediately cease using our service.

## 15\. Location of this Site

This Site is hosted and operated in the United States. However, we and our third party service providers may, in our effort to provide the Site, store Collected Information in the United States, or we may transfer it to, and store it within, other countries.

## 16\. Communication With Children

We encourage parents and guardians to spend time discussing with minors their online activity, so as to be fully familiar with the websites they visit and the apps they use. Our Site is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Site. If you are under 13, do not use this Site, register an Account, or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, email address, user name, or password.

It is possible, through fraud or deception, that we may receive personal information from an individual under the age of 13. If we are notified or otherwise become aware of this, we will take reasonable steps to delete that information in accordance with applicable law. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and you believe your child has provided personal information on our Site without your consent that you would like us to delete, please email us.

## 17\. Contact

Any inquiries about your rights under this Privacy Policy, or any other matters regarding your privacy, please [contact us](https://thestyleup.com/contact/).

## 18. Copyright Policy

To review the TheStyleUp Copyright policy, please [click here](https://thestyleup.com/copyright/).

We hope you have enjoyed reading our fascinating Privacy Policy. We are not sure why you have so much time on your hands, but congratulations on your life of leisure.

Last updated: May 28, 2018

Copyright 2004 – 2018 TheStyleUp.com All Rights Reserved.
